<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookBuzz</string>
    <string name="search_button">Search</string>
    <string name="search_query_placeholder">Enter a book title, author, or ISBN...</string>
    <string name="wlcmmsg">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home2">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="searchboxhint">Search By Books/Zipcode</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="remove">hello</string>
    <string name="abt"><u>About HelpDesk</u></string>
    <string name="aboutus1">The “Bookbuzz“ App is a interface for the citizens to locate emergency service providing agencies
(police station, hospital, fire station) on satellite Image within the periphery of current location so that
they can easily “reach” the agency in case of emergency. The App displays the current location of
the citizen on the Google Map along with details such as name of places, roads and major
landmarks. The App dynamically fetches details of all the agencies near the location of the citizen.
The App further provides the facility to “Tap” any of this service providing agencies and know the
route and road distance to reach there and contact numbers. Citizens can select any of these
numbers and make a call using the App to get immediate help. Also, HelpDesk provides “Tap on
Call” facility through which citizen can make an emergency call (100, 108, 101, and 181).</string>


    <string name="about_us2">The Mobile App has been developed on Android platforms. The HelpDesk App aims to provide
safety and security of the citizen anytime anywhere.</string>

</resources>